voluntary benefits are for employers who
care about their employees employers who
want to do more for their employees
while managing costs
voluntary insurance benefits our
additional group insurance benefits
offered on an optional basis over and
above your core group benefits coverage
the benefits are paid for by employees
through payroll deduction while you
don't pay the premiums you do leverage
your buying power for your employees
allowing them access to products at a
cost they often cannot get on their own
employees choose the type and amount of
coverage relevant for them and their
families and they pay 100% of the
premiums
don't worry that offering these optional
benefits will create a lot of effort on
your part
Sun Life has a unique team dedicated to
the promotion and communication of
voluntary benefits our team will work
closely with you to better understand
the needs of your organization we can
provide you with personalized employee
communication material to ensure that
your employees have the information they
need to make an informed decision
employees get the coverage they need at
a cost they often can't get on their own
and in addition to the financial benefit
of group pricing because your employees
are members of your group plan they can
often buy some amount of insurance
coverage without answering any health
questions it basically boils down to two
key points the strength of your group
buying power and the ability to get some
coverage without answering health
questions two major benefits with real
value to your employees all at no cost
to you they get the coverage they need
to help meet their unique needs and you
get the appreciation of making it
available all resulting in a stronger
employer employee relationship you can
learn even more about voluntary benefits
that you can provide to your employees
on our website at Sun Life dot see a
slash voluntary benefits
you